{
  "title": "Idioms with the phrasal verb pull",
  "questions": [
    {
      "id": 1,
      "question": "I was told that his chances for ........ the surgery were slim and if he did make it, he was given little hope for the next 24 hours.",
      "answers": [
        "pulling in",
        "pulling out",
        "pulling through",
        "pulling down"
      ],
      "correct": "pulling through"
    },
    {
      "id": 2,
      "question": "\"If you don't behave,\" my father said, \"I'm going to ........ right here, and you can wait by the side of the road tillwe come and get you.",
      "answers": ["pull over", "pull out", "pull through", "pull down"],
      "correct": "pull over"
    },
    {
      "id": 3,
      "question": "............ this period has given me the confidence and courage to pursue anything I want to despite the hard times.",
      "answers": [
        "Pulling off",
        "Pulling out",
        "Pulling through",
        "Pulling in"
      ],
      "correct": "Pulling through"
    },
    {
      "id": 4,
      "question": "Children should never be allowed to play in driveways because one never knows when someone may ........",
      "answers": ["pull over", "pull off", "pull through", "pull in"],
      "correct": "pull in"
    },
    {
      "id": 5,
      "question": "President Bush said last Saturday that ........ of Iraq now is not an option and rejected calls by some lawmakers to start bringing U.S. troops home.",
      "answers": [
        "pulling off",
        "pulling out",
        "pulling through",
        "pulling in"
      ],
      "correct": "pulling out"
    },
    {
      "id": 6,
      "question": "The M4 dissects the Downs and the rest of the county from east to west. The noise affects a wide area either side of the motorway and can ........ real estate prices.",
      "answers": ["pull over", "pull out", "pull through", "pull down"],
      "correct": "pull down"
    },
    {
      "id": 7,
      "question": "Cyclists should always ember that motorists will frequently cross the bike lane to park and ........ and out of rem driveways.  ",
      "answers": ["pull over", "pull out", "pull through", "pull in"],
      "correct": "pull in"
    },
    {
      "id": 8,
      "question": "Rescue teams rushed to the site and started ........ bodies from beneath the wreckage of the five-storied Al Ghaza hotel. ",
      "answers": [
        "pulling in",
        "pulling out",
        "pulling through",
        "pulling down"
      ],
      "correct": "pulling out"
    },
    {
      "id": 9,
      "question": "If you experience a breakdown, you should ........ to the side of the road and raise the hood of your car. ",
      "answers": ["pull over", "pull out", "pulling through", "pulling down"],
      "correct": "pull over"
    },
    {
      "id": 10,
      "question": "One of the most memorable images of the war was created when U.S. troops ........ the statue of Saddam Hussein in Fardus Square. ",
      "answers": ["pulled over", "pulled out", "pulled through", "pulled down"],
      "correct": "pulled down"
    }
  ]
}
